jmwant.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy – JMWant

JMWant.com Limited ("JMWant") is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you - e.g. arranging for an item to be sent to you or your customer, carrying out credit and other security checks and for the purposes of customer research and profiling or where we have your express permission to do so.

**Your Consent**

We will not disclose or sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission, but we are not responsible or held liable for the actions of third party sites from which you may have linked or been directed to the JMWant website.

**Communication & Marketing**

If you have made a purchase from our e-commerce platform, we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post, and telephone. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us by selected third parties when you become a member of JMWant.

All JMWant members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue receiving marketing material from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by visiting 'Your Details' in 'Your Account' on the JMWant website. You can access 'Your Account' once you register and login. You can also click on the "unsubscribe" link in any email communications which we might send you.

**Protecting Your Security**

We may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. This is done only to confirm your identity - a credit check is not performed and your credit rating is unaffected.

**Disclosures of Your Information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies or third parties only in the following circumstances:

• In the event that JMWant sells or buys any business or assets;  
• If JMWant or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets;  
• If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of JMWant, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Third Party Sites**

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Checking your Details**

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to JMWant, you may do so by contacting us. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.
